All right, congratulations.
好的 恭喜你
You've successfully wrangled a data set.
你已经成功整理了一个数据集
You've completed the entire wrangling process from gathering, to assessing,
你已经完成整个整理过程 从收集到评估
and through cleaning your data, which meant defining,
再到清理数据 即定义
coding, and testing cleaning operations.
编码和测试清理操作
After we are happy with the state of our data,
一旦我们对数据状态感到满意
and we are for the purpose of this walkthrough,
这也是我们演示的目的
now it's time to act on it.
现在是时候行动了
Which can mean analysis and visualization,
也就是分析和可视化
which we'll do right now.
我们马上要做的事情
What insights do we want to pull out of this data?
我们希望从这些数据中得到什么见解呢？
It's about job postings,
这与工作招聘有关
so maybe one thing that would be useful to know would be the percentage of postings
所以 可能我们需要知道 希望某个人立刻开始工作的百分比
that are looking for someone to start urgently, that is ASAP.
即 ASAP
That's one good angle for analysis and we now have
这是一个很好的分析角度 我们在 Startdate 列中
nicely clean data for that as well in our start date column.
有相应的很干净的数据
Because the focus of this course is data wrangling and not data analysis,
因为本课程的重点是数据整理 而不是数据分析
I'm just going to show you how the code works for this analysis here.
我即将向大家演示一下如何用代码进行分析
But there'll be a Jupyter Notebook below
但视频下方会有一个 Jupyter Notebook
this video for you to do it yourself if you'd like to.
如果你想的话 就可以自己操作
I encourage you to explore.
我建议你探究一下
When doing simple calculations like these,
做这样的简单计算时
I like to physically write down the numerator and denominator.
我喜欢手动写下分子和分母
It helps me to isolate the problem.
它有助于将问题分离出来
A percentage or fraction has a numerator and denominator.
百分比或分数有分子和分母
Again, we're looking for percentage of postings that
另外 希望某个人立刻开始工作
are looking for someone to start urgently,
的工作招聘百分比
that is ASAP. There we go.
即 ASAP 我们开始吧
Number of ASAP start dates divided by number of non-empty start dates.
ASAP Startdate 的数量除以非空 Startdate 的数量
All right, so here's how the code works.
很好 我们来介绍下代码的工作原理
We can use value_counts function again and pick out this ASAP count,
我们可以再次使用 value_counts 函数 挑出这个 ASAP 计数
6,856, which we should see here, and boom, great.
6,856 我们应该会在这里看到 很好
That's our numerator.
这就是我们的分子
And for the non-empty counts,
至于非空计数
we can just use the count function.
我们可以只使用计数函数
This excludes all of the NaN entries, 9,675.
这不包括所有 NaN 条目 9,675
That should be the same value we see in our info function, and yes.
这个值应该与我们在 info 函数中见到的相同 是的
StartDate, 9,675, non-null objects.
StartDate 9,675 非空值对象
Non-null meaning non-empty or non-NaN.
非空值是指非空或非 NaN
And all we have to do now is divide the two, numerator by denominator,
我们现在要做的是用分子 2 除以分母
and okay, approximately 71% of job postings have an urgent start date.
好的 约71%的招聘公告都要求立即上岗
Wow, okay, that's way higher than I would have guessed.
哇 好的 这一比例比我估计的要高一些
It would be awesome if we could make a chart showing
如果我们可以绘制一幅图表 肯定好极了
the distribution of start dates in the data.
因为它可以显示数据中开始工作日期的分布
That's where visualization comes in.
这时候就需要可视化了
Let's convert this analysis to a vis.
我们现在把分析转换成可视化
We'll create a pie chart and yes,
我们将创建一幅饼状图 是的
pie charts are okay sometimes.
饼状图有时候很有用
Again, I'll walk you through the code here since
另外 我将向你们详细解释下代码 因为
this course isn't about data visualization.
本课程并不讨论数据可视化
There again will be opportunity to code
视频下方有 Jupyter notebook 也有机会编码
along in the Jupyter Notebook below this video though, if you want to.
如果你想这么做的话
Okay, so here's our visualization code.
好的 这就是我们的可视化代码
Again, using our value_counts function and we attach this plot function.
我们还是用的 value_counts 函数 我们附上这个 plot 函数
We want a pie chart and press shift enter,
我们想要一幅饼状图 按 Shift+Enter
and that should be it. Actually, I lied.
这样就好了 实际上 我撒谎了
We need to put this little bit of code here first to
我们需要首先将这点代码放在这里
display the plots within our notebook,
以便在 Notebook 里显示曲线
and there is our pie chart.
这就是我们的饼状图
It's pretty ugly though because there are so many labels here addressing
虽然很不美观 因为有太多的标签
every single entry in the value counts output which you can see up here.
它们代表值计数输出结果中的每个条目 你可以在这里看到
There's so many. So, we'll import a library called numpy,
太多了 于是 我们导入一个叫 numpy 的库
short form or alias, np.
简写或别名叫 np
Then we'll create a custom array of
然后 我们将创建一个自定义标签数组
labels and this array will have the same length as our value_counts output.
这个数组的长度将与 values_counts 输出内容相同
The array will start off empty or i.e.
数组将以空组起始也就是说
this empty string here with type object.
这个带类型对象的空字符串
This gets into the nitty gritty details of
这揭示了 numpy 的基本细节
numpy so don't stress if this doesn't make sense to you currently.
所以 如果你目前不明白 也不要紧张
And let's make the first label in that array,
我们首先制作该数组中的第一个标签
ASAP, because the first entry is ASAP here.
ASAP 因为这里的第一个条目就是 ASAP
And check out that vis.
查看这幅图
That's a lot of urgent postings, 71% approximately.
这表示许多紧急工作招聘 大约71%